okay students settle down settle down
that includes you mr. Rodriguez do you
want to take the milk carton off of your
head thank you so much we have a special
guest today he's from this neighborhood
and he's a former gang member and he's
coming here this morning to talk to you
about life choices
so please give a warm Central High
School welcome to Donnie Herrera I used
to be just like you just like you you
you you used to clown around make fun of
the principal put milk on my head just
like you Rodriguez and then I got hit
with AIDS consequences
got into some real trouble boy
[Music]
stole from my mom and dad stole from my
own sister and then one day a piano fell
on my head what consequences gave me 88
concussions one for each key you think
I'm learning but no see I'm just like
you I got back out there
started making some real crimes homeboy
oh yeah oh yeah and then I got trampled
by a herd of buffalo what concert Glenn
says okay Donny uh I think we've had
enough done what my story I was like you
I decided to be cool to hang out with
some of the tough kids hmm you know who
I'm talking about they were hanging on
the streets late at night more than
cigarette smokers homes and then one day
I got shot out of a catapult that's it
into the mouth of a dragon students
everything you've heard here today is a
lie I don't lie anymore you're all
excused look at me I shouldn't even be
here
Thank You Paula Chester ease so I got
really deep in the crime I did a
drive-by at my own daughters quinceañera
yeah shut up everybody dead tell ya
then I got sucked into a wormhole
consequences that's it okay everybody
going I was in another dimension time to
introduce my own parents to each other
almost failed arm was disappearing and I
invented Johnny be good and my fear is
prom and at the last moment they kissed
and it came back faster we get away from
in the better nobody believed me we make
Greg really great
[Music]